What are you thinking about?
Guess.
I don't even need to guess.
Jiang Siyao.
Besides romance,
can't I think about national affairs?
You do,
but you don't say it.
I...
Don't feel pressured.
We are both fugitives now,
in the same boat.
Detective or not,
no more probing.
I'm not in the mood for that.
Then what are you in the mood for?
I'm simpler than you.
Looking at a scene like this...
Hehehe.
I really got dragged into this with you guys.
Blinded by
youthful hot-bloodedness.
What?
Sounds like
you regret joining us.
If right now,
I were still in the police station whitewashing the peace,
I would indeed regret it.
But honestly,
being blinded by hot-bloodedness
is indeed a bit reckless.
But if time could turn back,
I would still make the same choice.
So,
doing the right thing
is my patriotism.
What about your romance?
To be honest,
that little Taoist nun
has been unhappy lately.
How should I cheer her up?
How would I know?
True.
She's practically throwing herself at you,
and you're still playing hard to get.
What are you doing?
Forget it.
We have wine here,
let's speak our minds freely.
Come on.
Now thieves fill the Central Plains,
we should stand by the river with spears.
Then I'll follow up.
With a jade ruyi,
commanding with elegance,
astonishing everyone present.
Oh,
With a golden goblet,
pouring freely,
never getting drunk after a thousand cups.
Never getting drunk, never getting drunk.
Come on.
You've got some skills.
You taught me.
Come on.
Eat.
Look who's here.
A wanted fugitive
coming to my place in the middle of the night.
Could it be out of nostalgia for a former colleague?
I'm not just nostalgic,
I also remember an old acquaintance.
What are you trying to say?
Five years ago,
in Wei Xiaodong's case,
you knew who the real killer was all along.
The real murder weapon
was the Spear of Longinus from the girls' school.
You clearly knew,
but chose to hide it.
Look.
What is this?
I secretly took a picture of this
at the Thomas Church Girls' School.
It seems to be used by their church.
The wounds match.
If it weren't for you five years ago,
I wouldn't have botched that case,
and caused a wrongful conviction.
That was because you were too impulsive.
Don't shift the blame to others.
I didn't want to shift the blame to you.
I just feel sorry for you.
I don't need you to remind me.
Didn't you want to catch me for credit?
Come on.
You can do it now.
Forget it.
I still value our old friendship.
Just go.
I just wanted to remind you.
It's not too late to turn back now.
Do you know what I've been through?
Turn back?
Is it still not too late?
The last sum has been transferred.
The money went through William Bank.
Black Mass in the UK
has already received it.
Now the Jiuhe Gang and the foreign firm
have been taken over by Lei Lie's son,
Lei Zijun.
Everything is as usual.
Send someone to keep an eye on Lei Zijun.
At this time,
there can be no mistakes.
Don't worry, sir.
I've already sent someone over.
Have you been to the San Fasi Winery?
Where?
San Wasi.
Never been there.
What kind of filthy place is this?
Just stop getting involved
with them, okay?
Becoming the head of the Huo family is your destiny.
Protecting the Huo family is my destiny.
Sir,
what can I do for you?
There's an emergency.
My men reported that
Zeng Guoquan
is about to run away.
He found out so quickly
that we have the key evidence?
We can't let him get away.
But the current situation
poses no threat to him.
Why would he run?
After all these years of
corruption,
he knows he won't end up well.
He's been planning to live abroad for a long time.
Okay,
I understand.
Young Master,
we found them.
They are in a small courtyard
in Yangliu Village in the western suburbs.
Got it.
If we tell the police or the foreigners about this,
they're dead meat.
No rush.
Liangzi,
I want to ask you,
is my father really
helping foreigners smuggle illegal drugs?
Young Master,
but this Jiang Siyao,
she's no good.
She only took this case to get a promotion.
As a result, she investigated the foreigners
and hit a brick wall.
To appease the public anger,
she killed the Master
and pinned all the blame on him.
But
how come I heard that this Li Chengrui
and Jiang Siyao don't get along?
That's all an act.
Li Chengrui had an affair with Jiang Siyao six years ago.
Jiang Siyao was the one giving Li Chengrui orders.
Young Master,
let's hurry and tell the police about this.
No need.
I will avenge my father myself.
Why did Zeng Guoquan run away?
Someone has the evidence he holds.
He definitely has ties to the Satan Society.
Oh no,
Ningning ran away.
My lady,
what are you looking for?
How long are you going to keep pretending with me?
What are you talking about?
You were the one who told the police station
that we found the San Fasi Winery,
right?
I really forgot about that.
What exactly do you want to know?
You
are my biological father,
right?
My lady,
you can't just say things like that.
We are generations apart.
For the above two answers,
your expression when answering was exactly the same,
which means you are lying.
Alright.
About this San Fasi Winery,
I do know a thing or two,
but I was absolutely not involved.
I
have been investigating this Zeng Guoquan.
Come take a look at this.
Is this what you're looking for?
This
is the evidence of Zeng Guoquan
transferring his assets
through the William Trading Company.
If you want to help Jiang Siyao,
take it.
So,
you and Zeng Guoquan
are not working together.
You've also been investigating Zeng Guoquan.
That's right.
I
just care about you
and am afraid you'll be in danger.
You can take this ledger,
but I have one request.
You are not allowed to take risks alone.
Then send your troops
and come with me to save my senior sister.
No problem.
Here.
This is the Huo family's token.
The whole Fenghuang City will show us respect.
Take it.
Go.
Is what you just said
all true?
Ningning.
You only need to know
that for you,
I would die.